{
  "sheet_name": "Pentasize_8A",
  "bubble_id": "1742477953065x246493352504066050",
  "supabase_id": "605c5788-710f-49e9-b668-50fd2af00581",
  "total_answers": 104,
  "answers": [
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances that have Endocrine Disrupting (ED) properties according to Regulation (EU) 2017/2100, or Commission Regulation (EU) 2018/605, or contain substances included in the Candidate List of Substances of Very High Concern (REACH, Article 59 list) for having endocrine disrupting properties (Article 57(f)), in a concentrations exceeding 0.1% (w/w)? \n(Use LIST I & LIST III on https://edlists.org/ as a practical guide.)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit."
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain per- or polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFAS), defined as substances that contain at least one fully fluorinated methyl (CF3-) or methylene (-CF2-) carbon atom (without any H/Cl/Br/I atom attached to it), in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w)?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Commission Decision (EU) 2020/1803 - ANNEX of 27 November 2020 establishing the EU Ecolabel criteria for printed paper, stationery paper and paper carrier bag products.",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Dropdown",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes, the product meets the criteria. Declaration is available on request."
    },
    {
      "question": "Question #  DE-UZ 217a - Paper made from 100% recovered paper for paper bags and boxes",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Multiple text lines",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "OK"
    },
    {
      "question": "DE-UZ 217b - Paper bags and boxes made out of recycled paper\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Multiple text lines",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "OK"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product comply with the requirements of \"DGCCRF - Fiche Papiers et Cartons - January 2019\" about materials and objects made of paper and cardboard in the state of finished products intended to come into contact with foodstuffs within the meaning of the framework regulation (EC) 1935/2004?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances which are listed in Regulation (EC) No 1333/2008 on food additives, or listed in (EC) No 1334/2008 on flavourings (as amended)? \t\t\t\n\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product comply with Food Sanitation Act - Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare Positive Lists effective 1 June 2020 and amendments?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No."
    },
    {
      "question": "Product Description or Chemical Characterization ",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Single text line",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Pentasize 8A"
    },
    {
      "question": "Product Code/Reference",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Single text line",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "CAS 68784-12-3; CAS 577-11-7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Function in Application",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Single text line",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Paper sizing agent"
    },
    {
      "question": "Producer",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Single text line",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Aurorium"
    },
    {
      "question": "Production sites",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Single text line",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Aurorium UK Ltd."
    },
    {
      "question": "Add disclaimer (optional)",
      "question_number": "1.1.338",
      "response_type": "Multiple text lines",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "The foregoing statement is provided in good faith, is based on our current knowledge, and may be deemed accurate as of the date provided.  Users are advised to seek periodic confirmation and to undertake sufficient verification and testing to determine the suitability for their own particular purpose of any information referred to herein."
    },
    {
      "question": "Commission Decision (EU) 2019/70 - ANNEX I of 11 January 2019 establishing the EU Ecolabel criteria for graphic paper:\t\t\t",
      "question_number": "2.1.3",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes, the product meets the criteria. Declaration is available on request."
    },
    {
      "question": "Commission Decision (EU) 2019/70 - ANNEX II of 11 January 2019 establishing the EU Ecolabel criteria for tissue paper:\t\t\t",
      "question_number": "2.1.4",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes, the product meets the criteria. Declaration is available on request."
    },
    {
      "question": "Paper Products - Chemical Module",
      "question_number": "2.2.5",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes, the product meets the criteria."
    },
    {
      "question": "Tissue Paper - Supplementary Module",
      "question_number": "2.2.6",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "The product has not been assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Grease-proof paper - Supplementary Module",
      "question_number": "2.2.7",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "The product has not been assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Packaging for Liquid Foods",
      "question_number": "2.2.8",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "The product has not been assessed."
    },
    {
      "question": "Disposables for Food",
      "question_number": "2.2.9",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "The product has not been assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "DE-UZ-5. Sanitary paper products made of recycled paper",
      "question_number": "2.3.11",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No, the product does not meet the criteria"
    },
    {
      "question": "DE-UZ 14a - Recycled paper",
      "question_number": "2.3.12",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes, the product meets the criteria. Declaration is available on request."
    },
    {
      "question": "DE-UZ 14b - Finished products made from recovered paper for office and school demand\t\t\t",
      "question_number": "2.3.13",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes, the product meets the criteria. Declaration is available on request."
    },
    {
      "question": "DE-UZ 56 - Recycled cardboard\t\t\t",
      "question_number": "2.3.14",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "The product has not been assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "DE-UZ 72 - Printing and publication papers",
      "question_number": "2.3.15",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes, the product meets the criteria. Declaration is available on request."
    },
    {
      "question": "According to Regulation (EU) No. 528/2012 does the product contain biocidal active substances either intentionally added or non-intentionally via other raw materials?\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are the biocidal active substances used for in-can preservation (PT 6)?\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are the biocidal active substances listed in the Article 95 list, published by ECHA with the respective producer under PT 6?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "\"Only applicable for EU suppliers! Is the supplier of the active substance listed as an approved supplier in the Article 95 list for respective active substance? \"\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are the biocidal active substances used as slimicides (PT 12)?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Only applicable for EU suppliers! Is the supplier of the active substance listed as an approved supplier in the Article 95 list for respective active substance?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are the biocidal active substances used as Preservatives for liquid-cooling and processing systems (PT 11)?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "\"Only applicable for EU suppliers! Is the supplier of the active substance listed as an approved supplier in the Article 95 list for respective active substance? \"\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can the product be used for production of food contact articles from paper and paperboard (incl. incidental food contact)?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please specify general limitations which may apply to the product (e.g. dosage limitation): (Enter n/a if not applicable)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Multiple text lines",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Maximum 1%"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can the product be used for the production of articles from paper and paperboard, which comply with the requirements of article 3 and article 17 of the Framework Regulation (EC) No 1935/2004?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "BfR (Federal Institute for Risk Assessment) recommendation XIV. Polymer Dispersions in its current version",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "BfR (Federal Institute for Risk Assessment) recommendation XXXVI. Paper and Board for Food Contact in its current version.\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions: (XXXVI)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 1,
      "row_id": "1742514689505x800057976104419300",
      "answer": "68784-12-3\t"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions: (XXXVI)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Chemical name",
      "column_order": 6,
      "row_id": "1742514689505x800057976104419300",
      "answer": "3-Alkenyl(C15-20)-dihydrofuran-2,5-dione"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions: (XXXVI)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions and specifications",
      "column_order": 7,
      "row_id": "1742514689505x800057976104419300",
      "answer": "max 1.0%"
    },
    {
      "question": "BfR (Federal Institute for Risk Assessment) recommendation XXXVI/1. Cooking Papers, Hot Filter Papers and Filter Layers in its current version.",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "BfR (Federal Institute for Risk Assessment) recommendation XXXVI/2. Paper and Paperboard for Baking Purposes in its current version.\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "BfR (Federal Institute for Risk Assessment) recommendation XXXVI/3. Absorber pads based on cellulosic fibres for food packaging in its current version.",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product comply with the requirements of Commodities Act (Packaging and Consumer Articles) Regulation [Warenwetregeling verpakkingen en gebruiksartikelen] as amended, Hoofdstuk II \"Papier en Karton (Paper and paperboard)\"?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product comply with the requirements of Commodities Act (Packaging and Consumer Articles) Regulation [Warenwetregeling verpakkingen en gebruiksartikelen] as amended; Hoofdstuk X \"Deklagen (Coatings)\"?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product comply with SR 817.023.21 „Ordinance of the EDI on articles and materials for food contact“ of 01 May 2017, especially Annex 10 „Authorized substances for the manufacture of printing inks“?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions, as well as all limitations given in column 7-9:\t\n*Include \"use\" from column 5 and classification (A or B) from column 6.\t\n\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 1,
      "row_id": "1742514769567x569756126024302600",
      "answer": "68784-12-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions, as well as all limitations given in column 7-9:\t\n*Include \"use\" from column 5 and classification (A or B) from column 6.\t\n\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions & specifications",
      "column_order": 6,
      "row_id": "1742514769567x569756126024302600",
      "answer": "Column 5 = AD\nColumn 6 = B"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product comply with the Ministerial Decree of 21 March 1973 (as amended) concerning hygiene requirements for packages, containers and tools destined to come into contact with food or substances for personal use?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are components used in the manufacture of the product, which are listed with specific limits in the EU Regulation on plastics materials and articles (EU) 10/2011 as amended?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can the product be used for the manufacture of food contact articles made from paper and paper board otherwise complying with 21 CFR § 176.170 “Components of paper and paperboard in contact with aqueous and fatty foods”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.170)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 4,
      "row_id": "1742514868302x622752617601695700",
      "answer": "68784-12-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.170)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions and specifications",
      "column_order": 7,
      "row_id": "1742514868302x622752617601695700",
      "answer": "1% max dry weight"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can the product be used for the manufacture of food contact articles made from paper and paper board otherwise complying with 21 CFR § 176.180 “Components of paper and paperboard in contact with dry foods”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.180)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 4,
      "row_id": "1742514891795x268724214862184450",
      "answer": "68784-12-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.180)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions and specifications",
      "column_order": 7,
      "row_id": "1742514891795x268724214862184450",
      "answer": "1% max dry weight"
    },
    {
      "question": "21 CFR § 175.105 “Adhesives”, provided that the respective use conditions described in § 175.105 are met?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "21 CFR § 175.300 “Resinous and polymeric coatings”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "21 CFR § 176.300 “Slimicides”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "21 CFR § 176.200 “Defoaming agents used in coatings”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "21 CFR § 176.210 “Defoaming agents used in the manufacture of paper and paperboard”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product have a Food Contact Notification (FCN) in effect?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is the product in accordance with the  “National food safety standard – General safety requirements of food contact materials and articles” GB 4806.1-2016 as amended?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does your product fulfill the requirements of the “National Food Safety Standard – Papers, Paperboard Materials and its Articles for Food Contact” GB4806.8-2016 as amended?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does your product comply with the requirements for food contact paper and board materials and their products according to the National Standard of the People's Republic of China GB9685-2016 (Standard for uses of Additives in Food Contact Materials and Articles), issued Oct. 19th 2016 as amended?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions (GB9685)\n",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 4,
      "row_id": "1742514964328x653172621450936300",
      "answer": "68784-12-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions (GB9685)\n",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "SML (mg/kg)",
      "column_order": 6,
      "row_id": "1742514964328x653172621450936300",
      "answer": "30 mg/kg based on maleic anhydride"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions (GB9685)\n",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions & specifications",
      "column_order": 9,
      "row_id": "1742514964328x653172621450936300",
      "answer": "1% max"
    },
    {
      "question": "Other Standard (GB) for resin or any positive listing for resin by MOH Announcement which applies to the product?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can the product be used for the production of articles from paper and paperboard, which comply with the requirements of MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 03/92?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 39/19 - Technical regulations on positive list of additives for plastic materials and polymeric coatings intended to contact food, in its current version?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable."
    },
    {
      "question": "MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 40/15 - Technical regulations on materials, packages and cellulosic equipment destined to be in contact with foods, in its current version?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "(40-15) If yes, please give all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 4,
      "row_id": "1742515012332x193553325227245570",
      "answer": "68784-12-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "(40-15) If yes, please give all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "FCM number of regulation, if any",
      "column_order": 5,
      "row_id": "1742515012332x193553325227245570",
      "answer": "MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 03/9203/"
    },
    {
      "question": "(40-15) If yes, please give all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions & specifications",
      "column_order": 9,
      "row_id": "1742515012332x193553325227245570",
      "answer": "1% max on dry fiber basis"
    },
    {
      "question": "MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 41/15 - Technical regulations on cellulosic materials for hot cooking and filtration, in its current version?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 42/15 - Technical regulations on materials, containers and cellulosic equipment destined to be in contact with food during cooking or heating in an oven, in its current version?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 02/12 - Technical regulation on the positive list of monomers, other starting substances and authorized polymers for plastic equipment in contact with food, in its current version?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances classified as carcinogenic (C), mutagenic (M), or reprotoxic (R), according to Annex VI of the CLP Regulation (EC) No 1272/2008 as amended, in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w) or a specific concentration limit?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain SVHC substances listed in the Candidate List of Substances of Very High Concern for Authorization (Article 59 list) on the ECHA homepage, in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w)?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances subject to Authorisation according to Annex XIV of the REACH Regulation (EC) No 1907/2006 as amended in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w) or a specific concentration limit mentioned in the relevant regulation?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances subject to Restrictions according to Annex XVII of the REACH Regulation (EC) No 1907/2006 as amended in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w) or a specific concentration limit mentioned in the relevant regulation?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain priority substances listed in the Water Framework Directive (2000/60/EC) or the Directive on Environmental Quality Standards (Directive 2008/105/EC) in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w) or a specific concentration limit mentioned in the relevant regulation?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain persistent organic pollutants (POP) in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w) or a specific concentration limit mentioned in the relevant regulation?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain more than 100 ppm (as sum) of lead, cadmium, mercury and hexavalent chromium, therefore the product can not be used in packaging material with regard to CONEG and Directive 94/62/EC on packaging and packaging waste?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain elements restricted by Standard EN 71-3, or organic contaminants as restricted by Standard EN 71-9, in its current version?\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not evaluated"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances included in the California Proposition 65 list (Safe Drinking Water and Toxic Enforcement Act of 1986)?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and/or reasonably not expected to be present."
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances listed in the PIDSL List in concentrations exceeding the declarable limit?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the delivered product and/or its production site or line have a Kosher certification?",
      "question_number": "6.1.1",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the delivered product and/or its production site or line have a Halal certification?",
      "question_number": "6.1.3",
      "response_type": "Select one",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are substances prohibited during Passover (chametz and kitniyot) intentionally added to the product? ",
      "question_number": "6.1.5",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are substances of animal origin (including dairy and dairy based ingredients) intentionally added to the product, or known contaminants in the product?",
      "question_number": "6.2.7",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is there a concern that the product contains BSE (Bovine Spongiform Encephalopathy) or TSE (Transmissible Spongiform Encephalopathies) specified risk material as defined in the Decision 97/534/EC, EMEA/410/01 and current EU legislation?",
      "question_number": "6.3.9",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is ethanol (CAS 64-17-5 ) intentionally added to the product?",
      "question_number": "6.4.10",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are food allergens as defined by Regulation (EU) No 1169/2011 intentionally added to the product, or known contaminants in the product?",
      "question_number": "6.5.12",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are food allergens as defined by US Food Allergen Labeling and Consumer Protection Act of 2004 intentionally added to the product, or known contaminants in the product?",
      "question_number": "6.5.14",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are nanomaterials as defined by EC Recommendation 2011/696/EU intentionally added to the product? ",
      "question_number": "6.6.16",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are GMOs, or substances produced from GMO but no longer containing GMO, as defined by Regulation (EU) No 1829/2003 and amendments intentionally added to the product?",
      "question_number": "6.7.18",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain Mineral Oil Hydrocarbons (MOH)?",
      "question_number": "6.8.20",
      "response_type": "Dropdown",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details regarding the content of MOAH (Mineral Oil Aromatic Hydrocarbons, C16-35) and PAH (Polyaromatic Hydrocarbons):",
      "question_number": "6.8.23",
      "response_type": "Multiple text lines",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are conflict minerals regulated by the Dodd-Frank Act or Regulation (EU) 2017/821 intentionally added to the product, or are conflict minerals used during the production of the product?",
      "question_number": "6.9.24",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are Palm Oil or Palm Kernel Oil, or components derived from Palm Oil or Palm Kernel Oil intentionally added to the product?",
      "question_number": "6.10.26",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No, not intentionally added."
    }
  ]
}